<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="77104" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="RenderMastery" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="More render options." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="More render options." /-->
	<LongDescription>
		Render Mastery
		Render Mastery is a powerful tool for enhancing your gaming experience, providing you with a wide range of settings to fine-tune your graphics and performance. Utilizing Colossal and Game.Rendering.Utilities, Render Mastery offers a comprehensive suite of options through Game.Settings and Game.UI.Widgets.

		This mod replaces the older versions 'ReRenderingOptions', 'Dynamic Resolution Extended' plus 'Performance Squeezer' from third party modding sites.

		Features
		Advanced Settings Tab: Access advanced settings under the "Advanced" tab.
		Basic Settings Tab: Explore basic settings under the "Basic Tab."
		Graphics Settings
		Adaptive Dynamic Resolution Scale: Adjust the adaptive dynamic resolution scale.
		Level of Detail: Force-tune and switch the level of detail settings.
		Global Quality Level: Adjust the global quality level of rendering.
		Global Texture Mipmap Limit: Set the global texture mipmap limit.
		Shadow Distance: Control the distance at which shadows are rendered.
		Shadow Cascades: Adjust the number of shadow cascades.
		Shadow Projection: Set the shadow projection mode.
		Shadow Near Plane Offset: Adjust the shadow near plane offset.
		Realtime Reflection Probes: Toggle realtime reflection probes.
		Billboards Face Camera Position: Toggle billboards facing the camera position.
		Anti-Aliasing: Adjust anti-aliasing settings. This feature is experimental and might conflict with other settings.
		Async Upload Time Slice: Set the async upload time slice.
		Async Upload Buffer Size: Set the async upload buffer size.
		Terrain Detail Density Scale: Adjust the terrain detail density scale.
		Terrain Pixel Error: Set the terrain pixel error.
		Terrain Basemap Distance: Set the terrain basemap distance.
		Terrain Detail Distance: Set the terrain detail distance.
		Terrain Tree Distance: Set the terrain tree distance.
		Terrain Billboard Start: Set the terrain billboard start.
		Terrain Fade Length: Set the terrain fade length.
		Terrain Max Trees: Terrain max trees. Also an experimental feature.
		Troubleshooting
		All settings are stored in \AppData\LocalLow\Colossal Order\Cities Skylines II\ModsData\RenderMastery.

		The settings menu also includes a support button that links to my Discord server for immediate assistance. Additionally, there is a reset button that restores settings to their default values.

		Enjoy!
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Logo.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/Logo.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.0.3" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Settings troubleshoot 1.0.3" />
	<!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
	<ExternalLink Type="" Url="" />
</Publish>
